https://www.mobilegpsonline.com/mgpsstore/index.php?main_page=privacy

About Us
Welcome to our Store!
Mobile GPS Online is an Ottawa-based company, founded in 2002 by Dr. -Ing. Detang Zhong. With more than 30 years experience in academic research institutions, high-tech companies and self-motivated business and marketing development plus close partnerships with several popular GPS hardware vendors and system developers, we have the expertise to meet your GPS application needs. Mobile GPS Online became a subsidiary of Geoidsoft Inc. in 2016 after serving our happy clients for 14 years. As always, our commitment is to offer you high quality and effective solutions for your GPS needs and applications with the ultimate experience in convenience, value and satisfaction. Our mission is high quality product, competitive price and outstanding support.
How to Order
Shipping Info
Return Policy
Contact Us
0
- $0.00
Categories
GPS/GNSS Survey Antenna2GPS/GNSS Repeater5GPS/GNSS Receiver22GPS/GNSS Tracker1GPS/GNSS Datalogger2GPS/GNSS OEM Module12Marine GPS/GNSS/AIS19Sport GPS/GNSS1GPS/GNSS SplitterGPS/GNSS Amplifier4GPS/GNSS Antenna40GSM/LTE Antenna16WiFi/Wlan Antenna25VHF/UHF Antenna2Combination Antenna38Cable and Connectors2Software & Maps5VIP Custom Product3New Products ...Featured Products ...All Products ...
Manufacturers
Please Select
Fugawi - Northp..
GlobalSat
LOCOSYS
Mobile GPS Onli..
San Jose Techno..
TOJOIN
Information
About Us
Create Account
How to Order
Return Policy
Shipping Information
Post Sale Services
Privacy Notice
The following policy describes how Mobile GPS Online Store collects, stores, uses and distributes information that is submitted to us by individuals.
By using our site, or providing information to us in other formats, you consent to the collection and use of your information as we have described in this policy.
USE OF INFORMATION
Our goal is to collect, use and disclose only that information reasonably required to enable us to provide the particular product or service that you have requested, to improve our website, products or services, to maintain our customer lists, to respond to your inquiries or feedback or to conduct the particular activity for which you have submitted information.
We will use information we collect to compile aggregate statistics, traffic patterns and related site information, to conduct internal research and marketing. We will not provide your information to any other third parties except for reasons listed in the section of the Important Exceptions below.
We may contact you from time to time to offer additional products or services. If you do not want to be contacted please contact us at the address provided below. However, if we remove you form our contacts list, please note that you will not receive product update information.
HOW TO CONTROL THE INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE TO US
If you want to remove your information from our database, please email privacy@mobilegpsonline.com. and inform us of your request. However, you can always use postal mail to make your request to:
Privacy CoordinatorMobile GPS Online Store3151 Strandherd Drive P.O.Box 45535 Ottawa, OntarioCanada K2J 0P9Tel: 613-220-7908Fax: 613-823-0926Please allow 4 to 6 weeks for us to update your information.IMPORTANT EXCEPTIONS
We may disclose information to a third party without your consent if we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, other site users or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities or if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is required by and in accordance with the law or judicial process.
We will also disclose your information to third party agencies providing credit card processing, fraud detection and order fulfillment services for purchases from our site and in connection with a corporate re-organization, a merger or amalgamation with another entity, or a sale of all or a substantial portion of our assets provided that the information disclosed continues to be used for the purposes permitted by this Privacy Policy by the entity acquiring the information. We will retain information to the extent we believe is required by law.
OUTSIDE PARTIES AND SITES AND INTERNET SECURITY
We may provide links to third party websites or offer third-party vendors and websites. The privacy policies of these third parties are not under our control and may differ from ours. The use of any information that you may provide to any third party, or the use of "cookie" technology by any third party, will be governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the website that you are visiting. If you have any doubts about the privacy of the information you are providing on another website, we recommend that you contact that site directly for more information and review its privacy policy.
The Internet is not a secure medium of communication and privacy cannot be ensured. We cannot assume any responsibility, nor will we be liable, for any damages you or a third party may suffer as a result of the transmission of any information that you make to us through the Internet, or as a result of information you provide to third party websites linked to our site.
CHANGES TO OUR POLICY
If we find it necessary or desirable to change our privacy policy in the future, we will post changes as soon as they go into effect so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how it will be used, and under what circumstances we will disclose it. Any change to this policy will become effective on the date the change is posted. You can determine this date by looking at the date at the bottom of this web page. We recommend that you print a copy of this policy for your reference and revisit this policy from time to time to ensure you are aware of any changes. Should you not agree with any changes, your sole remedy is to remove your information from our database. Please contact us at the address noted above to do so. LET US KNOW WHAT YOU THINK
If you have any questions or comments about your privacy and Mobile GPS Online Store, please let us know by contacting us at privacy@mobilegpsonline.com.
GENERAL
We control the site (excluding third party linked sites) from our company offices within the province of Ontario, Canada. The law of the province of Ontario (and applicable Canadian federal laws) will apply to all issues and matters relating to or arising from your use of this site. You agree to submit to the personal jurisdiction and venue of the courts of Ontario located in Ottawa, Ontario or any federal court located in Ontario. Choice of law principles and the United Nations Convention for the International Sale of Goods and any legislation implementing such Convention are hereby expressly excluded. Last updated March. 01, 2005.
Back
Bestsellers
JCA001 GPS Active Antenna$12.98
RA-50 GPS L1 Band GPS Signal...$69.98
RV-16 High Gain Permanently Mount...$34.98
JCA003 Screw Mount GPS
Active...$12.98
Who's Online
There currently are 4 guests online.
